[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What gives Christians true meaning and peace in this life and the next?",
    "answer": "That we belong to God.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": true
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Who is God?",
    "answer": "God is the Father, the Son, and the Holy Spirit—one God in three persons, eternally existing in love and unity.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": true
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What is God like?",
    "answer": "God is love, holy, eternal, unchanging, the Creator of all things.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": true
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Why did God create us?",
    "answer": "God created us out of His overflowing love to share in His love and for His glory.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": true
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "How did God create us, and what is our purpose?",
    "answer": "God created us in His image to glorify Him.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": true
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What else did God create?",
    "answer": "God created everything, and all He made was very good",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": true
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What does it mean to glorify God?",
    "answer": "To love Him above all and to obey His commands.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": true
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What is the greatest command in God’s law?",
    "answer": "To love the Lord with all our heart, soul, mind, and strength, and to love our neighbour as ourselves.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": true
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What is the law of God stated in the Ten Commandments?",
    "answer": "1. You shall have no other gods before me. 2. You shall not make for yourself an idol. 3. You shall not misuse the name of the Lord your God. 4. Remember the Sabbath day by keeping it holy. 5. Honor your father and your mother. 6. You shall not murder. 7. You shall not commit adultery. 8. You shall not steal. 9. You shall not give false testimony. 10. You shall not covet.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": true
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Can anyone perfectly obey God’s law?",
    "answer": "No, because of sin, no human can obey it perfectly.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": true
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Were we created unable to keep God's law?",
    "answer": "No, but because of Adam’s sin, we are all born with a sinful nature, unable to keep God’s law or turn to God in faith on our own.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "How did Adam’s sin affect all humanity?",
    "answer": "Through Adam, all people inherit a sinful nature, making us naturally inclined to sin.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What gives Christians true meaning and peace in this life and the next?",
    "answer": "That we belong to God.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "Who is God?",
    "answer": "God is the Father, the Son, and the Holy Spirit—one God in three persons, eternally existing in love and unity.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What is God like?",
    "answer": "God is love, holy, eternal, unchanging, the Creator of all things.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "Why did God create us?",
    "answer": "God created us out of His overflowing love to share in His love and for His glory.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "How did God create us, and what is our purpose?",
    "answer": "God created us in His image to glorify Him.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What else did God create?",
    "answer": "God created everything, and all He made was very good",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What does it mean to glorify God?",
    "answer": "To love Him above all and to obey His commands.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What is the greatest command in God’s law?",
    "answer": "To love the Lord with all our heart, soul, mind, and strength, and to love our neighbour as ourselves.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What is the law of God stated in the Ten Commandments?",
    "answer": "1. You shall have no other gods before me. 2. You shall not make for yourself an idol. 3. You shall not misuse the name of the Lord your God. 4. Remember the Sabbath day by keeping it holy. 5. Honor your father and your mother. 6. You shall not murder. 7. You shall not commit adultery. 8. You shall not steal. 9. You shall not give false testimony. 10. You shall not covet.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "Can anyone perfectly obey God’s law?",
    "answer": "No, because of sin, no human can obey it perfectly.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "Were we created unable to keep God's law?",
    "answer": "No, but because of Adam’s sin, we are all born with a sinful nature, unable to keep God’s law or turn to God in faith on our own.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "How did Adam’s sin affect all humanity?",
    "answer": "Through Adam, all people inherit a sinful nature, making us naturally inclined to sin.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What gives Christians true meaning and peace in this life and the next?",
    "answer": "That we belong to God.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "Who is God?",
    "answer": "God is the Father, the Son, and the Holy Spirit—one God in three persons, eternally existing in love and unity.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What is God like?",
    "answer": "God is love, holy, eternal, unchanging, the Creator of all things.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "Why did God create us?",
    "answer": "God created us out of His overflowing love to share in His love and for His glory.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "How did God create us, and what is our purpose?",
    "answer": "God created us in His image to glorify Him.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "What else did God create?",
    "answer": "God created everything, and all He made was very good",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What does it mean to glorify God?",
    "answer": "To love Him above all and to obey His commands.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "question": "What is the greatest command in God’s law?",
    "answer": "To love the Lord with all our heart, soul, mind, and strength, and to love our neighbour as ourselves.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "question": "What is the law of God stated in the Ten Commandments?",
    "answer": "1. You shall have no other gods before me. 2. You shall not make for yourself an idol. 3. You shall not misuse the name of the Lord your God. 4. Remember the Sabbath day by keeping it holy. 5. Honor your father and your mother. 6. You shall not murder. 7. You shall not commit adultery. 8. You shall not steal. 9. You shall not give false testimony. 10. You shall not covet.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "question": "Can anyone perfectly obey God’s law?",
    "answer": "No, because of sin, no human can obey it perfectly.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "question": "Were we created unable to keep God's law?",
    "answer": "No, but because of Adam’s sin, we are all born with a sinful nature, unable to keep God’s law or turn to God in faith on our own.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "question": "How did Adam’s sin affect all humanity?",
    "answer": "Through Adam, all people inherit a sinful nature, making us naturally inclined to sin.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "question": "What gives Christians true meaning and peace in this life and the next?",
    "answer": "That we belong to God.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "question": "Who is God?",
    "answer": "God is the Father, the Son, and the Holy Spirit—one God in three persons, eternally existing in love and unity.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "question": "What is God like?",
    "answer": "God is love, holy, eternal, unchanging, the Creator of all things.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "question": "Why did God create us?",
    "answer": "God created us out of His overflowing love to share in His love and for His glory.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "question": "How did God create us, and what is our purpose?",
    "answer": "God created us in His image to glorify Him.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "question": "What else did God create?",
    "answer": "God created everything, and all He made was very good",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "question": "What does it mean to glorify God?",
    "answer": "To love Him above all and to obey His commands.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "question": "What is the greatest command in God’s law?",
    "answer": "To love the Lord with all our heart, soul, mind, and strength, and to love our neighbour as ourselves.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "question": "What is the law of God stated in the Ten Commandments?",
    "answer": "1. You shall have no other gods before me. 2. You shall not make for yourself an idol. 3. You shall not misuse the name of the Lord your God. 4. Remember the Sabbath day by keeping it holy. 5. Honor your father and your mother. 6. You shall not murder. 7. You shall not commit adultery. 8. You shall not steal. 9. You shall not give false testimony. 10. You shall not covet.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "question": "Can anyone perfectly obey God’s law?",
    "answer": "No, because of sin, no human can obey it perfectly.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "question": "Were we created unable to keep God's law?",
    "answer": "No, but because of Adam’s sin, we are all born with a sinful nature, unable to keep God’s law or turn to God in faith on our own.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 48,
    "question": "How did Adam’s sin affect all humanity?",
    "answer": "Through Adam, all people inherit a sinful nature, making us naturally inclined to sin.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 49,
    "question": "What gives Christians true meaning and peace in this life and the next?",
    "answer": "That we belong to God.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 50,
    "question": "Who is God?",
    "answer": "God is the Father, the Son, and the Holy Spirit—one God in three persons, eternally existing in love and unity.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 51,
    "question": "What is God like?",
    "answer": "God is love, holy, eternal, unchanging, the Creator of all things.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 52,
    "question": "Why did God create us?",
    "answer": "God created us out of His overflowing love to share in His love and for His glory.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 53,
    "question": "How did God create us, and what is our purpose?",
    "answer": "God created us in His image to glorify Him.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 54,
    "question": "What else did God create?",
    "answer": "God created everything, and all He made was very good",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 55,
    "question": "What does it mean to glorify God?",
    "answer": "To love Him above all and to obey His commands.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 56,
    "question": "What is the greatest command in God’s law?",
    "answer": "To love the Lord with all our heart, soul, mind, and strength, and to love our neighbour as ourselves.",
    "youtube": "",
    "unlocked": false
  }
]